( Watch on Kissasia.vip )
[Episode 4]
[Xiqiao Ferry]
Chieftain Zhong,
are you here to watch a show?
Immobilized by Zhan Zhao's
Heavenward Crane Strike,
I can't move a muscle.
What about the Iron Blood Guards?
Iron Blood Guards has a rule.
They never kill the innocent.
We won't break the rule for the Xiuluo Cult.
For Xiuluo Cult?
It's for His Lordship's great cause!
Then show me His Lordship's command token.
What?
Fine.
I see how it is now.
You just want to reap the benefits
without lifting a finger.
I didn't step in,
so you don't have to split your glory.
Now,
all the credit belongs to you.
You don't even spare your partner.
The Yunying Sect people only know
some lightness skills, flashy but useless.
They'll never amount to anything.
He died for me.
That was an honorable end for him.
- Don't move.
- Mom, Dad!
- Please, save my son!
- Save my brother!
One more step,
and I'll snap his neck.
I beg you. Save my son!
Don't worry.
I will definitely save him.
Zhan Zhao,
Heavenward Crane Strike can help you leave.
But if you use it to save that child,
I'm afraid you'll never cross this ferry.
At noon,
the poison in your body will flare up.
Without Heavenward Crane Strike as a protector.
Death
is coming for you.
I knew it.
You wouldn't dare kill me.
The Southern Knight became an official.
You have your titles and your gold,
but put the law's chains on your own neck.
Don't you find it ridiculous?
You pride yourself on being chivalrous,
yet you don't even have the courage
to kill me and uphold justice.
If Liu Hong Yi knew you were like this,
I'm afraid he'd also resent your cowardice.
I've poisoned him
with over ten Xiuluo Cult poisons.
None of them will kill him instantly.
But they will slowly melt his internal organs.
He will rot from the inside out
until he turns into a pool of blood.
The Yunying Sect
has never turned a blind eye to villains.
I killed Mo Dao.
My master's soul
can finally know peace.
Past the farmhouse ahead
is Xiqiao Ferry.
Once across that river,
it is no longer under Xiangzhou's jurisdiction.
Another 20 miles
will lead to Yincheng Town,
where the Guanghua Army is stationed.
Their commander, Meng Kui, is my friend.
He'll send men to escort me all the way north.
With a fast horse,
I can reach the capital
in less than two days.
Got him?
Yes, got him.
Did you search him thoroughly?
Zhan Zhao doesn't have that object.
I've sent men to find his companion.
Wait till he wakes.
Then make him tell us where his companion is.
To make Zhan Zhao tell you?
You must be dreaming.
Chieftain Zhong,
instead of sitting here
waiting for him to wake up,
why don't you use your head
and go find some clues?
Since Zhan Zhao was caught,
every crossing is being watched more closely.
Still no sign of his companion.
Besides waiting for him to talk,
what else can we do?
Commander Shao,
would you show me how?
Where did you find Zhan Zhao?
My men encountered Zhan Zhao and his companion
on the mountain road to Xiqiao Ferry.
Later, I found him hiding in an abandoned barn
near the ferry.
What did Zhan Zhao's companion
look like?
- Wei Feng.
- Yes.
Report to Commander Shao.
What did Zhan Zhao's companion
look like?
Yes.
Commander Shao,
it was a young man around 18 or 19.
Quite handsome,
with impressive martial arts.
He barely made a move.
We were finished before we could fight back.
His weapon was very strange.
It was entirely black,
like a mace.
Commander Shao,
His Lordship ordered us to capture him alive.
If you wish to kill Zhan Zhao,
report to His Lordship yourself.
The ferry capture of Zhan Zhao was hard-won.
As Zhong Xiong stood by and did nothing,
we suffered many casualties.
Even Mo Dao died.
I'm wondering
if Zhong Xiong is dragging his feet on purpose.
He doesn't want to go after that companion.
Zhong Xiong thinks very highly of himself.
Aside from His Lordship,
he rarely respects anyone else.
To be hauled to the ferry like that,
before so many eyes,
unable to move a finger.
He must have been so ashamed.
If he loses Zhan Zhao's companion now,
he won't be able to explain himself.
So, Commander, you mean...
It's not that he won't go looking for them.
He's as thick as you are.
Neither of you knows where to go.
Zhong Xiong is such a fool.
Zhan Zhao's companion was clearly in the barn.
Yet he let them escape right under his nose.
Zhan Zhao's companion
has indeed impressive lightness skills.
Or the footprints wouldn't be so light.
But look at the prints.
One's deep, the other's light.
He may have wounded his leg.
He may have already left Xiangzhou.
That's impossible.
We've locked down all the routes to Xiangzhou.
He won't escape, not even if he had wings.
We did lock down all the routes
before the battle,
but after capturing Zhan Zhao,
we overlooked one place.
Xiqiao Ferry.
Zhan Zhao made a fool of Zhong Xiong.
Zhan Zhao saw all of this coming.
When Zhong Xiong discovered
the letter wasn't on him,
he thought the desperate battle at Xiqiao Ferry
was just to buy time
to allow his companion
to escape with the letter.
Zhan Zhao is clever.
I'll give him that.
Even though he's severely wounded
and all alone,
he's still more than a match
for Zhong Xiong and the others.
No wonder Liu Hong Yi searched for him.
It's just a pity
that I won't have the chance
to cross swords with such a formidable man.
So we know his companion's leg is hurt.
Hunting one young man blind,
it's like searching the woods
for a single leaf.
Not really.
Have you forgotten?
That person carries
a weapon that is rare in this world.
Did you already know who he is?
You think
Zhan Zhao would still be breathing
without Linglong Honey
from Linglong Manor?
So that is...
To Xiqiao Ferry.
Cross the river and keep pursuing.
Let's go.
She's disappeared?
We argued yesterday.
By dusk, no one could find her.
She knew I would come today
to send the betrothal gifts.
Is she fleeing the wedding on purpose?
[Huo Tian Xing, Chief of the Linglong Manor]
Uh...
I thought what we had,
growing up together...
No bond could ever match it.
Does she not feel the same way?
Nephew, don't overthink it.
I scolded Ling Long. Nothing more.
She's likely run off to stay with her kin.
We won't delay the wedding date.
Take care.
Young master, your tea's gotten cold.
- Let me get you a fresh, hot one.
- No need.
How do I get to Yincheng Town?
Yincheng Town?
Go outside and head straight west.
You'll be there in 20 miles.
But look, it's almost dark.
There won't be any lodging left
if you set out this late.
I see.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Everyone, out.
You too.
Yes.
Ling Long.
Even if you quarreled with Uncle-Master Huo,
you shouldn't have run away from home.
Do you know how worried I was?
It seems my father hasn't told you the truth.
I didn't run away from home
because I quarreled with him.
I just don't want to marry you.
Ling Long.
[Huo Ling Long,
Young Lady of the Linglong Manor.]
Let go of me.
You left without a word for so many days.
Uncle-Master Huo is so worried.
I've said it before.
I won't stay if he forces a marriage on me.
He just didn't believe me.
If you don't want to marry me so soon,
you could have told me.
I'll tell Lord of Xiangyang
to postpone it for months.
Why you do this?
I'll say it one last time.
I don't want to marry you.
Whether you want to marry me or not,
you must come back with me.
We can clear things up in front of your dad.
Clear things up?
Are you forcing me back
to clear things up about the marriage,
or for what's in my hands?
I came here because I'm worrying about you.
Why are you hunting Zhan Zhao?
I received orders to capture him.
My duty is to follow orders.
Ling Long, youth makes you blind
to what men truly are.
How can you trust a man
you've only known for days?
Don't you think that's too dangerous?
You must be fooled by his title
as the Southern Knight,
and fell for his hypocritical act.
Besides, how do you know he's really Zhan Zhao?
You know very well
whether he's Zhan Zhao or not.
What I've experienced in these few days
is more than in ten years at the Manor.
I can tell who is a hypocrite.
Ling Long.
Fine.
Arguing was not my strength, Ling Long.
Let's say Zhan Zhao is a good man.
He helps those in need. My apologies.
I shouldn't have followed orders blindly.
I apologize to you.
But have you thought about this?
People like Mo Dao are no good men.
If Zhan Zhao were to die under torture,
no matter how much injustice there is,
he won't be able to see it,
let alone do anything about it.
Perhaps Zhan Zhao is acting on other's orders.
Simply because of a friend's request,
he might die at the hands of
a bunch of nobodies.
Isn't that too high a price?
If it were in the past,
I would have definitely thought you were right.
What exactly is this object about?
Whether you've sided with the wicked
and wronged him.
We'll know when the court sees the evidence.
Why are you so impatient?
Why are you hunting him with such an uproar?
I know you're here for what I have.
Can't the mask come off after all these years?
- How impudent!
- Can't keep up the act any longer?
Then you'd better think carefully.
If you offend me,
will you get Linglong Eye?
What nonsense are you talking?
I want to marry you
because we are meant for each other.
What does it matter with the Linglong Eye?
It's common knowledge that
the Huo family's dowry
features the Linglong Eye,
the priceless family treasure.
Isn't this why you rushed into the betrothal?
Just admit it. It's not shameful.
Huo Ling Long.
I'll give you one last chance.
I've shown more than enough respect
to you and to Linglong Manor.
Now, come back with me,
and I'll pretend nothing happened.
What if I refuse?
You can't escape
from me.
- Hand it over and come back with me.
- Never.
Two days. And now you're ready
to throw your life away for him?
Did you get a crush on him?
Nonsense.
There is nothing between us.
It's better that way.
His Heavenward Crane Strike is
the secret technique of the Ding family.
He's clearly not Ding Zhao.
So he must be the Ding family's
future son-in-law.
Don't make a fool of yourself.
Since you refuse to hand it over,
I'll have to take it by force.
[Bai Yu Tang, Jinmao Rat]
My apologies.
Just slipped.
You continue.
What are you laughing at?
I'm laughing because
a grown man is fighting a lady
whose strength and size are no match for yours,
and you're still struggling.
Isn't that funny?
How long have you been watching?
I've been here eating plums all along.
You're the ones who barged in.
Shouting, cursing, and fighting.
This is my private family matter.
Sorry for disturbing you.
Forgive me.
Stop talking nonsense.
He's just a wretched little man.
I have nothing to do with him.
I know.
I accidentally overheard everything.
His goal this time
isn't to force you into marriage.
It's for an object you're carrying.
You'd better not meddle.
Cross swords with me for a stranger?
That's a fool's bargain.
I think you've misunderstood.
I never said I'd interfere.
You're not going to save her?
Why should I save her?
Her martial arts are far superior to yours.
She can defeat you with ease.
No need for my help.
Lady,
you have such great skills.
How can you not even defeat him?
It makes no sense.
Please don't mock me.
I'm no match for him.
What are you afraid of?
With just a little guidance from me,
you can defeat him.
I wonder if you have the patience,
and the grace to accept defeat.
I know her martial arts well.
If you want to guide her,
do it.
What exactly do you want?
What else can I do?
You don't know the trick of it.
Let me put you on the right path.
But I'm no match for him.
We've matched countless times since childhood,
and I've never won once.
Those were just practice.
Now it's a life-or-death struggle.
Of course you can't win
if you only think about winning.
What you need to think about
is how to kill him.
My leg is injured now.
Even less likely to kill him.
Come on. Forget about your leg injury.
You must use all your strength
to overcome your own cowardice.
Weapons are meant for killing.
Every time you draw your mace, mean to kill.
Never stop until the enemy is dead.
Besides,
you're holding a peerless divine weapon.
What a fine mace.
His sword is no match for yours.
So what is there to be afraid of?
It's been quite a while.
Commander Shao hasn't returned yet.
Is it that hard to catch a young girl?
What a blockhead.
That's Commander Shao's fiancée.
How could he get rough with her?
He has to use sweet words
before she'll come back.
How about... we go back and take a look?
Are you crazy? If you go back now
and walk in on them,
he'll smash your ugly head in.
You'd better think this through.
I won't show any mercy this time.
What a coincidence.
I won't show any mercy either.
Here it is.
That's your real skill.
Ling Long, are you serious?
I just said I wouldn't show any mercy.
It's you who underestimated me.
He's just bluffing.
No need to fear him.
It seems you've backed the wrong side.
Didn't you say you wouldn't intervene?
Are you going back on your word?
Actually, I was entrusted
to escort this lady to the capital.
You mean Zhan Zhao?
Exactly.
After being injured,
he sent me a message via pigeon,
asking me to come.
Then you are...
Didn't you just say it?
Zhan Zhao's Heavenward Crane Strike
is Ding's secret technique.
The Ding Twins?
Correct. I am Ding Zhao Hui.
My brother, Ding Zhao Lan, and the others
are on their way here.
As you said,
Zhan Zhao is the Ding family's son-in-law.
If anything happens to him,
the Ding family won't stand by and do nothing.
I'm sure you've seen
Zhan Zhao's Heavenward Crane Strike.
He's trained well.
He's my brother's equal in that skill.
As for me,
I'm slightly less skilled,
but enough to hold you off for a while.
When my brother arrives,
you can match yourself against him.
How about it?
My Heavenward Crane Strike.
Not bad, right?
Are you really Zhan Zhao's friend?
I know you want to save Zhan Zhao.
But I reckon this man's curs will be here soon.
We need a plan.
Plus, your leg is wounded.
We must not stay here long.
Let's leave first.
Strange.
Where are they?
This was torn from Commander Shao's clothes.
[Tomorrow at dawn. The hostage exchange.
Luosi Cave. Jiangjia Village.]
Damn it. They've taken Commander Shao.
- Let's go.
- Go!
Apply these herbs to your wound.
For the pain. And to speed the healing.
Thank you.
You know medicine?
A man who's always on the road
must know how to tend to simple wounds.
Your leg won't let you fight like that again.
If you want to save him, end this quickly.
Didn't you say your brother was coming?
How many men did he bring with him?
I lied.
You believed that?
So everything you said just now was a lie?
Most of it was true.
For example, you can defeat him.
That part is true.
Clearly I lost.
That part is not true.
That isn't over.
After this battle,
you've overcome your fear of him.
Defeating him is only a matter of time.
Besides,
that was as good as he'd ever get.
I don't think he'll make any more progress.
You said you are Ding Zhao Hui.
Is that true?
Of course it's true.
The Zhan family and we
have shared blood for generations.
Zhan Zhao and I grew up together.
He and my sister were betrothed as children.
My father even taught him
the Ding family's secret technique.
Though they aren't married yet,
he's my future brother-in-law.
Anything you wish to know about him,
I have the answers.
[The hostage exchange. Jiangjia Village.]
Chieftain Zhong, say something!
Commander Shao,
a peerless hero,
captured by a little girl?
That's hardly possible.
This was clearly torn from his clothes.
What's left to doubt?
We've searched every inch of the ferry.
There's no sign of them.
What else could it be?
We bled to catch Zhan Zhao.
We can't just let him go.
His Lordship gave a strict order.
Zhan Zhao can't leave Xiangzhou.
His Lordship values Commander Shao.
He won't just leave him to die.
Then send word back to His Lordship.
We'll wait for his command before we act.
The kidnappers say the exchange
will happen at dawn.
If we send word back now,
when does the reply come back?
You must be on purpose.
Commander Shao's life is indeed important,
but are His Lordship's orders not important?
Why are you here?
His Lordship thought you were shorthanded,
so he sent me to help.
I thought capturing Zhan Zhao
would be the end of it.
But one move, taking Shao Ji Zu,
and you've lost all sense of direction.
Well then, Master Zhi Hua,
what brilliant plan do you have?
Why don't you tell us,
and give us some sense of direction?
If you had caught Zhan Zhao in Yicheng County,
would we even have all this trouble now?
Even if the sky falls,
I shouldn't be the one most anxious, right?
If that object in Zhan Zhao's hands
reaches the court,
that's when the sky truly falls.
If he ruins
His Lordship's painstaking work in Xiangzhou,
all of us here
will be buried with him.
Master Zhi,
speak freely, whatever is on your mind.
As long as Commander Shao is rescued,
I can't speak for others,
but the prefectural court is yours to command.
In the battle at Xiqiao Ferry,
Chieftain Zhong, you exhausted yourself
capturing the Southern Knight.
This time,
you should stay here.
Can you spare half of Iron Blood Guards here
to march with Feng Shao and me?
How is it? Anyone suspicious?
Not at all.
Did we look in the wrong place?
It can't be wrong.
The cloth says the exchange
will be at Jiangjia Village.
Check the riverbank.
Right. Let's go check the riverbank.
Yes.
There's a boat over there.
Go take a look.
Commander Shao!
It's a trap! Get back!
Get back!
Where is Zhong Xiong?
Zhong Xiong!
Give me a hand! Hurry!
Careful.
What happened? What happened here?
With so many people watching him,
he must've done something really big.
Zhan!
Go. I'll be right behind you.
[Yanling]
I'm taking Zhan Zhao with me.
Do yourself a favor.
Stand down.
Are you sure there were two of them?
One was wearing white.
Yes. The other person
was holding a very powerful weapon.
It's the Yin Yang An.
Commander Shao,
why didn't you tell us sooner
that Zhan Zhao's helper is from Linglong Manor?
Didn't you seal a betrothal with them?
Why are they helping an outsider?
Ling Long was now bewitched by a villain.
No wonder your previous attempts all failed.
Could it be
the betrothal to Ling Long stayed your hand?
I miscalculated that.
But how did they find out
that Zhan Zhao was here?
Chieftain Zhong,
after we left,
did you withdraw all Iron Blood Guards?
Of course.
Zhan Zhao had already been captured.
Why are my brothers still being kept there?
They followed the Iron Blood Guards here.
Then who exactly is this young man in white?
So young, but already so bold and clever.
When I first met him,
he said he was Ding Zhao Hui.
- Ding Zhao Hui?
- Impossible.
I've fought him before.
It's not the Ding family's martial arts style.
He's definitely lying.
This man's martial arts are superb.
And his moves are very strange.
I can't tell which sect his skills belong to.
His lightness skill is excellent.
It rivals even that of the Huo family.
Where are we going now?
Xiqiao Ferry?
Try to cross the river before they catch up.
They're riding the crown's finest horses.
We've got a wagon
and a wounded man.
How can we outrun them?
Besides,
I don't think the man inside
can handle this rough ride.
His breath is so weak.
No different from a dead man.
What did you feed him?
Linglong Honey.
It can't save his life,
but at least it eases his pain.
Useless.
Old Souls at First Glance
has wounded him deeply.
Then what should we do?
You seem so worried about him.
Give me a hand.